>> Brian Holt: 目前的问题 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Questions so far?
嗯。 >> 扬声器 2: 是，所以
Yeah.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, so
我相信 12 行，还没有呈现 div id 根吗 ?
I believe on line 12 you still have
that div id root not rendered?
11 号线路抱歉
On line 11, sorry.
>> Brian Holt: 对。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yep.
>> 演讲者 2: 在哪里 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Where did that go?
>> Brian Holt: 未呈现的位置?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Where did
the not rendered go?
>> 扬声器 2: 是。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah.
>> Brian Holt: 当你说呈现时，就像这里
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: When you say render,
like here,
它会把里面的任何东西都炸掉
it blows away anything
that's inside of it.
所以它只会覆盖它
So it just overrides it.
举个例子，比如说我放进来，
So for example, like if I put in here,
抛出新错误， >> Brian Holt: And
throw new Error,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
然后我回到这里你会看到它其实是蓝色的
then I go back over here,
you'll see it actually just blue it away.
还在虚张声势
It's still blued away.
> > Brian Holt: 因为它确实试图渲染，但让我们
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Because it did
try to render it, but let's,
如果你把它放在外面， >> Brian Holt: 那么
actually if you put it outside of that,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Then
它会不会被渲染的对吧
it'll say not rendered, right?
因为它没被清除
Because it didn't get cleared out.
因此，这有助于了解您的 JavaScript 正在装入。
So this just kind of helps to see
that your JavaScript is loading.
不是，只是我做的事，不一定是最好的做法
Not, it's just something I do, it's not
necessarily like a best practice or
任何类似的事情
anything like that.
>> Brian Holt: 这是最佳的错误。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is the best
error right here, by the way.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，其他问题?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, other questions?
嗯。
Yeah.
>> 扬声器 3: 在应用程序声明中，您将返回我所使用的内容
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: In your app declaration
you have it returns something which I'm
假设当你在后台运行的时候，任何神奇的 React 都在做。
assuming is whatever magic React is doing
when you run that in the background.
然后我们又在另一个 " React.create " 元素中传递
But then we're passing at
another React.create element?
这有什么用
What's up with that?
>> Brian Holt: 是，好的问题。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, good question.
所以，让我们谈谈 React.create 元素获取的三个参数
So let's talk about the three parameters
that React.create element gets
第一个是什么标签，对吧 ?
the first one is what kind of tag is it,
right?
你可以在这里看到，我给它打了 3 次， reet.createElement。
So you can see here, I've called it
three times, react.createElement.
我在这儿打过电话我在这儿打过电话
I've called it here, I've called
it here and I've called it here.
>> Brian Holt: 第一个是什么元素。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: The first one
is what kind of element it is.
这是一个 div ，这是一个 h1，这就是所谓的组合组件，
This is a div, this is an h1, and this is
what you would call a composite component,
这就是你和我创作的组件对吧
which is a fancy way of saying a component
that you and I created, right?
第二个，现在是空对象，空对象，
The second, which right now is
an empty object, empty object, and
没有定义我们只是没在这里定义对吧
undefined, cuz we're just
not defining it here, right?
您要提供组件的所有属性。
Is all of the attributes that
you want to give the component.
所以如果我想让这件事
So if I wanted this to
have ID of something
重要的， >> Brian Holt: 现在
important,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now
这个标识将被传递到这个区
this ID is going to be
passed into this div.
为了证明我的意思如果我刷新一下然后过来
So just to prove my point,
if I refresh and come over here, and
我看 " 检查元件"
I look at Inspect Element,
你可以在这里看到这个现在其实有一个重要的概念。
you can see here that this now actually
has an idea of something important.
好的，这是 DOM 元素上要放置的属性。
All right, so this is the attributes that
are gonna be put on the DOM element.
或者如果我把它给应用，这将是
Or if I gave it to app,
this is going to be the attributes that
将会进入我可以使用的应用
are going to pass down
into app that I can use.
我们一会儿再谈这个
We'll talk about that in a second.
但只要说这就是你想要传递给孩子的东西
But suffice to say this is whatever you
want to pass into the child element,
这件案子里的
in this case, the div.
第三个是孩子。
The third one is the children.
这里的 div 是 h1，好吗 ?
So inside of div here is an h1, all right?
所以这第三个是什么，都是你的孩子
And so that's what this third one is,
it's whatever children you
要被传递到这个特定的元素，对吗 ?
want to be passed into this
particular element, right?
那么，在这种情况下， h1 的子代只是针对 " 采用我 " 的文本，对吗 ?
So in this case, the children of the h1
is just to text Adopt Me, right?
但我完全可以在这里停车的对吧
But I totally could have
pulled a span in here, right?
或者类似的东西
Or something like that.
现在，这可以是奇异的，也可以是数组。
Now, this can be either singular,
or this can also be an array.
Czz 一个 DIV 可以有 15 个孩子，对吧 ?
Cuz a DIV can have 15 children, right?
所以我也可以，就这么做吧
So here I could also have,
let's just do it for
有趣的， >> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
fun,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
现在我有两个人收养我
Now I have two h1s with Adopt Me,
所以如果我回到这里，你可以看到有两个 h1s 被传递到这个。
so if I go back over here, you can see
that there are two h1s passed into this.
> > Brian Holt: 在技术上，这不一定是数组，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So technically
this doesn't have to be an array,
你可以在所有参数中通过这些参数，它仍然有效。
you can actually just pass these in
all the parameters, it still works.
>> Brian Holt: 它叫做变量 Verity，它是一个愚蠢的计算机科学
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's called variable
verity, which is a stupid computer science
我学会了我想给你留下的印象
word that I learned and
I wanted to impress you with.
>> Brian Holt: 这就意味着它可以接受更多的额外的周边和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It just means that it
can accept as many extra perimeters and
它会把所有孩子都用作孩子
it'll use all of those as children.
现在我在你的大脑模型中将它作为一个数组，因为它会使它更简单
Now I would say in your brain model this
as an array because it'll make it simpler
因为我们不会再像这样写那么久了
in your brain, because we will not be
writing React like this for very long, so.
我想指出的是，在网上有人为我提出这个问题之前。
Just wanted to point that out, before
someone online points it out for me.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 好的，我们要回去了
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
we're gonna go back to this.